<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ooo_calc_export scriptAuthor="vjl" scriptURL="http://www.digitalimprint.com/misc/oooexport/" scriptUpdate="2011-03-02" scriptVersion="2.2.0_qdxml">
  <ooo_sheet num="1">
    <ooo_row><column_1>loc_key</column_1><column_2>value</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_01_FromStart_a</column_1><column_2>怪我によって目覚め、難破した体が痛みに震える。敵はあなたが死んだと思って捨てて行ったようだが、それでもここでうかうかしてはいられない。力を振り絞り、死ぬ気で体を動かして再び意識を失った場所へと向かった。</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_01_FromStart_b</column_1><column_2>数時間後に意識を取り戻した。殴られて出血までしているが、まだ生きている。
傷跡は長く残りそうだ…。あなたは自身の無謀さを呪い、これからはもっと慎重になることを誓った。</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_02_GEP_a</column_1><column_2>あなたは骨も折られ地面に倒れ伏した。痛みで意識が遠のこうとした直前に誰かがあなたの上に立っていることに気づいた。あなたを守っているのだ！痛みで意識が霞む中、暖かい声があなたに届く。「おお、起きたか！今日はまだ君の死ぬ時ではない。
私と一緒に居なさい、私が世話をしよう。」</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_02_GEP_b</column_1><column_2>星と焚火はあなたの熱い心の中で踊る。
あなたの目は開いていて、あなたは自分自身が安全だと感じる。暖かい焚火が鳴り響き、その横にメモと神秘的な瓶が立てかけられていた。
あなたは一人ですが、少し前に誰かがここにいたような気がする…</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_03_HyenasDefeat_Cherso_a</column_1><column_2>あなたは腕を上げ、あなたに向かって吠える動物からあなたの傷つきやすい喉を守り、そして死のためにあなた自身を支えます...牙が足に喰い込み、そして、あなたは地面を引きずられる。すべての岩石と隆起に叩きつけられ、痛みを引き起こす。そしてあなたは暗闇の中に引きずられる...</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_03_HyenasDefeat_Cherso_b</column_1><column_2>あなたがようやく目を開いたとき、貧弱な探検家のものであろう、半分食べられた足を見る。ハイエナは空腹であり、遠吠えをしている。夕食の準備が整ったことは明らかだ！</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_04_BanditSouthCampPrisoner_Cherso_a</column_1><column_2>あなたは無意識から目覚め、そして気付く。盗賊があなたの手を結びつけ、他の囚人の列につなげていく。
鞭によりあなたの腕は叩きつけられ、夜通し走るように命じられる。捕獲者はあなたを走らせる。あなたと他の囚人たちはふらふらと走る。そして、ついに、あなたの視界に盗賊たちのキャンプが...</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_04_BanditSouthCampPrisoner_Cherso_b</column_1><column_2>仲間の囚人の悲惨な叫び声は、鉄の檻の中に押し込まれるにつれて空気を満たし、そしてあなたは完全な暗闇の中で残された。煮込んでシチューにするために。あなたは仕事を得る。刑務所の扉からボルトを無理矢理にでも押し出す仕事を。
それは大変な仕事だが、結局あなたは成功した。脱出する時が来た！
</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_05_Immaculate_a</column_1><column_2>あなたは骨も折られ地面に倒れ伏した。痛みにより意識が遠ざかる時に、誰かがあなたの上に立っているのを感じる。あなたを守っている！暖かい声が痛みの霞を通してあなたに届く。&quot;生きているか？答えなさい！&quot;</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_05_Immaculate_b</column_1><column_2>あなたは数時間後に目覚めた。地下で。頭を上げると、視界の隅を動くものが。
それは2本足で歩く、巨大な獣で、その体には赤く脈動をする血管が沿っている。
</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_05_Immaculate_c</column_1><column_2>その怪物はあなたを救ったにちがいない！それは本を手に持ち、静かに笑っている。あなたが立ち上がろうとするが、あなたの意識は数分間再び消える。</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_06_Hermit_Cherso_b</column_1><column_2>数時間後、あなたは老人がパイプを吸っている小さな小屋で目を覚ました。
&quot;特に意味はない。優しさの風に感謝しなさい、それはあなたが必要としている時に私に吹いたのだから。
もっと注意を払うことであなたはうまくいくでしょう。hmmm？&quot;</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_07_CierzoInn_a</column_1><column_2>もう我慢できない、まさに呼吸の行為が困難になりつつある。
あなたの意識が薄れるにつれて、痛みはあなたの体を包み込む…</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_07_CierzoInn_b</column_1><column_2>Cierzo's innの温かい香りがあなたを迎えた。誰かがあなたを死の瀬戸際に見つけ、あなたを健康状態に戻した。
少なくともあなたはまだ生きてるが、風邪をひいてしまったようだ...
</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_08_CierzoDoors_b</column_1><column_2>あなたは、Cierzoからの狩人を見て目覚めた。あなたの口の中に水を注いでくれている。
彼女に寄りかかって、あなたはなんとか生き残った。死にかけだが、Cierzoに戻ってきた。彼女はお礼を受け取らず、去っていった。あなたの肩をたたいて。</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_09_BanditSouthCampTrashed_Cherso_a</column_1><column_2>あなたは無意識から目覚め、そして気付く。盗賊があなたの手を結びつけ、他の囚人の列につなげていく。鞭によりあなたの腕は叩きつけられ、夜通し走るように命じられる。捕獲者はあなたを走らせる。あなたと他の囚人たちはふらふらと走る。そして、ついに、あなたの視界に盗賊たちのキャンプが...</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_09_BanditSouthCampTrashed_Cherso_b</column_1><column_2>強制された死の行進。吐き気の波。そしてあなたは混乱に陥る前に、冷たい硬い地面に嘔吐した。あなたが戻る時まで、あなたは一人だ。
彼らは病気の囚人には役に立たない...</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_10_BanditNorthCampPrisoner_Cherso_b</column_1><column_2>あなたは目を開き、そして見つける。道路に沿って跳ている、囚人と死体が入ったカートの中に自分自身を。
無意識があなたを連れて行くように、あなたは Montcalm 族によって捕虜にされたことを知っている...</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_10_BanditNorthCampPrisoner_Cherso_c</column_1><column_2>数時間後、 Montcalm の村の中に閉じ込められたあなたは再び目を開いた。
彼らがあなたの死体を外にぶら下がっている他の人たちに加わえようと意図しているのは間違いありません！</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_12_CD2_Entrance_a</column_1><column_2>怪我によって目覚め、難破した体が痛みに震える。あなたは一人だが、しかし確実に安全ではない。歯を食いしばり、あなたは安全のために自分を外に引きずり出すことができる。</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_19_BanditNorthCampTrashed_Cherso_c</column_1><column_2>死の寸前から目が覚めた、死体があなたの上に積まれている。多大な努力を払って、あなたは自分を解放し、荒い木製の壁の外にでた。Montcalm の部族はあなたを死者と間違えたようだ...</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_20_VendavelPrisoner_a</column_1><column_2>目を開けると、Kazite の女性があなたの両目の間に刀を向けている。彼女はあなたの手を縛り、あなたを目隠しし、そして行進を強制するので、あなたは抵抗できない。あなたの周りの至る所で、略奪が行われている音や声がする。</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_20_VendavelPrisoner_b</column_1><column_2>あなたを捕獲した者はあなたを独房に入れ、あなたの後ろに冷たい鉄の棒を打ちつける。
&quot;これが奴隷になる方法だ！私たちの命令通りに働け、あなたは食べ物と水を手に入れることができる。
それとも仕事を拒否するのなら、「穴」へ！&quot;</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_21_TroglodytesDefeat_a</column_1><column_2>戦う力がなければ、Troglodytes があなたを取り囲み、彼らの野蛮な言葉をさえずり、彼らの洞窟にあなたを運ぶ。大きく明るく照らされた部屋にあなたを投げ入れる。腐った肉の嫌なにおいが鼻孔を満たす。
</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_21_TroglodytesDefeat_b</column_1><column_2>Troglodytes は、火の上の大きな石の鉢の周りに集まり、時々あなたを見つめている。空腹なのだ。突然、洞窟の中に雑音が響き渡り、モンスター達は動きを止める。
モンスター達は槍をつかみ、突撃していく。あなたを一人のこして。</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_22_Watchers_a</column_1><column_2>あなたの体と心は壊れた。あとは死による解放を待つだけだ...奇妙な紫色のオーラがあなたの周りを旋回し、あなたは夢のような流れに乗り、星と幽霊のような人物を通過しながら、あなたは彼らに自分自身を与える。</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_22_Watchers_b</column_1><column_2>鈍い痛みに目が覚める。魔法のオーラは消えたわけでは無い、今、あなたはそれらの出所を感じることができる。あなたは Ley Line の監視人の世話で、Conflux Mountain の下の中央の部屋にいる...</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_23_GhostPrisoner_a</column_1><column_2>身を守るすべが無い。あなたを圧迫する、幽霊のような姿が接近してくるのを止めることができない。
それはあなたが認識できない言語で話し掛けてくる。しかし意図は明らかだ - 抵抗するな！それはあなたの腕をつかみ、あなたを引きずりながら Ghost Pass を通る。脱出しようと試みるのならば、武器をつかめ…</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_23_GhostPrisoner_b</column_1><column_2>あなたの旅は、古い独房で終わる。扉がずっと昔に落ちた壊れた独房で。幽霊はあなたの腕を離し、向きを変え、扉を所定の位置に押し込み、空中で「鍵」をひねるように動かす。</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_23_GhostPrisoner_c</column_1><column_2>独房にしるされている標識は古い言語だが、「処刑のマーク」であると推測するのは簡単だ。あなたは幸運な星たち感謝する。その幽霊が古い思い出に閉じ込められていて、推論も思考もできないことに...</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_25_CierzoHome_b</column_1><column_2>あなたは Cierzo の Lighthouse で古い家のおなじみの香りに目を覚ました。暖かいベッドに横になっている。あなたのバックパックは傍に置かれていた。
誰かがあなたを家に持ち帰り、手当てしてくれたのだ。どれだけ長く気を失っていたのか...</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_31_BergInn</column_1><column_2>あなたは自分が Berg の宿のベッドに包まれているのに気づく。どのくらいの日数、気を失っていたのだろうか。
宿屋の主人は、あなたの銀に対して、あなたの滞在の代金を払うよう、手助けをしてくれた。それ以外は問題ない。健康だ。
.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_32_BergDoors</column_1><column_2>あなたが次に目を覚ましたとき、あなたは Berg からのハンターによって運ばれていた。彼は街に帰る途中だ。
彼は街の入り口で優しく降ろしてくれた。
 “気を付けろ、お前はマンティコアの夕食になるところだったんだぞ！”</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_39_LevantInn</column_1><column_2>あなたは Levant’s inn で絹のシーツに包まれて目を覚ました。数日後には健康に戻る。あなたの財布がどれほど明るくなったかで判断すると、治療や食べ物も安くなっていないようだ。さて、あなたは生きている。また戦うために！
</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_40_LevantDoors</column_1><column_2>あなたを援助するために傭兵会社をもたらすもの、それは純粋な運だ。
傭兵の集団は Levant の門にあなたを安全に連れ戻す。あなたの安心のために！無償で！
それから彼らは陽気に旅館へと行く。彼らがあなたの命をどのように救ったかについて、奉仕する女の子たちに自慢しようとしていて、支払いを要求することは無かった...</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_43_HMD2_Entrance</column_1><column_2>あなたは湿地で目を覚ました。
Ash Giants はあなたを彼らの村の外へ捨てたのだ。
あなたは彼らを手助けすることはできないが、この失礼な扱いに少し戸惑いを感じることはできる。</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_49_MonsoonInn</column_1><column_2>あなたが過去数日間の熱い夢から目覚めたときに、甘い香の香りが辺りに漂っていた。宣教師が Monsoon の宿にあなたを連れていき、去っていったのだ。宿主はあなたの治療のために、あなたの財布からお金を使っているが、少なくともあなたはまだ生きている。
</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_50_MonsoonDoors</column_1><column_2>あなたの目が開くと、あなたは自分自身が Monsoon の門の壁に支えられていることに気づくだろう。安全だ。あなたの救世主を探しあたりを見回す。群衆の中に輝く白い装甲の誰かが消えるのを見た...
</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_51_CierzoHomeTuto</column_1><column_2>気絶は素早く訪れる。そして、あなたは何かに襲われる夢を見る。小さな悲鳴とともに、あなたはベッドから飛び出す。
自分がどこにいるかを認識し、あなたは救済されたのだと安堵した。
あなたは家の古いベッド、Cierzo の Lighthouse に戻った。</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_51_CierzoHomeTuto_b</column_1><column_2>Yzan は、あなたをあなたの家族のいる lighthouse に連れ戻したのだ。あなたの痛む肉体だけが、あの難破船は悪夢ではなかったとあなたに伝える。</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_52_Vigile</column_1><column_2>怪物のまぼろしはあなたの熱っぽい夢を満たし、そして、何かが、あなたを、容赦なく執拗につけまわす。ねじれた悪夢だ。あなたは目覚める。妄想と恐怖の感覚に圧倒されて。あなたは上に Vigil クリスタルの1つを見つける... Elatt’s の名前でどうやってここに来たのだ？</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_53_Watchers2</column_1><column_2>山の頂上で無意識のうちに紫の草があなたを取り囲む。生命にかかわる損傷は、フードを被った男によって包帯をされていた。彼は振り向くことなく、山の壁沿いの扉に入り、静かに去って行く...
</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_54_JustWakeUp</column_1><column_2>何時間も意識の外で彷徨い、やっとあなたは立ち直ることができた。あなたが気を失っている間、傷つけられた様子はない。幸運だ…</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_55_SavedByGhosts</column_1><column_2>You wake up to see a butterfly resting on your nose, someplace quiet. As you pull yourself up you notice a trio of ghosts guarding you...yet they soon vanish as if they were never there...It would seem that the Ancestral Memories sent you aid in your time of need.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_56_SavedByGiants</column_1><column_2>The smell of ash and cinder wakes you. The wide grin of a travelling Giant merchant greets you as you open your eyes. “Haloo, there, small human! That was a close call, no? You are lucky Silvernose came to your rescue!”</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_56_SavedByGiants_b</column_1><column_2>He pats a large backpack. “I have things in here for to prevent you from being in trouble again! My prices are very good, small human!” It would seem that your alliance with the Giants has just saved your life.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_57_RobbedByThugs</column_1><column_2>You snap awake with a yelp, feeling someone reaching into your various pouches. The hooded man pilfering your belongings jumps to his feet and sprints away at an impressive pace with his two companions.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_57_RobbedByThugs_b</column_1><column_2>A quick check confirms the worst. He’s helped himself to a lot of your valuables. You wonder how these criminals knew to find you out here...You sense that someone must have sent them after you, but who?</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_58_Elatt</column_1><column_2>As you see your life flash before your eyes, a brilliant light blinds you. As your eyes adjust once more, you find yourself laid on the ground someplace safe outdoors. Elatt’s intervention has no doubt saved your life.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_59_SteakosaursDefeat</column_1><column_2>Loud screeches startle you awake. You’ve been dragged into a cave, surrounded by the lizards of the marsh, screeching and fighting one another for the right to feast on you! You must flee, if you value your life!</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_61_GiantsVillage</column_1><column_2>The first thing you notice, as you come to your senses, is that you are in a bed much too large for you. An Ash giant speaks in a rough, incomprehensible language as he tends to you. It would seem your alliance with them has saved your life.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_62_MonsoonHome</column_1><column_2>Dull aches wake you from your days-long comatose state. Your injuries and needs have been seen to, and you have been returned to your home in Monsoon. Whoever tended to you left no sign of their identity, nor have they taken payment.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_64_InsectsDefeat</column_1><column_2>The blood rushes to your head as you awaken upside down, cocooned by massive predatory bugs. With great difficulty, you free yourself and fall to the hive floor. If you do not intend to be dinner tonight, you should make yourself scarce from this place.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_65_CorsairsCampPrisoner_a</column_1><column_2>Desert bandits pounce on you and tie you up in a sack, before dragging you across the sand dunes. You pass out from the heat and lack of air more than once.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_65_CorsairsCampPrisoner_b</column_1><column_2>You wake up deep underground, at a bandit’s camp in an old crumbling mine. No doubt they intend to use you as slave labor. You cut the ropes that bind you on a nearby rock and prepare to make your escape!</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_66_CorsairsHivePrison_b</column_1><column_2>Hours later you wake up and break free of the bag, only to find yourself in a prison cell surrounded by deadly insects. With great effort, you manage to force the bolts on the door off and stumble out of the cell. It’s time to beat a hasty retreat, before the insects grow hungry!</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_67_LevantHome</column_1><column_2>You’re first aware that an army medic is pouring water into your mouth, then that you’re back at your manor in Levant. The medic declines payment, only saying “It’s been taken care of.” You’ve been out for days, but you’re still mostly in one piece.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_68_Slums</column_1><column_2>A dark, lonely alley greets you as you open your eyes. Someone from the slums of Levant must have found you and brought you to safety. A quick check confirms that they’ve helped themselves to your pouch of money as repayment while they were at it!</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_69_VendavelTrashed</column_1><column_2>Your head aches, resting on rotten driftwood, your body submerged in water. A glance upwards shows only a small speck of light from the top of “The Hole”. You were exceptionally lucky to survive a fall like that.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_69_VendavelTrashed_b</column_1><column_2>With great effort, you swim in the murky water until you see a ray of light... You’ve escaped the Fortress of Vendavel, but paid dearly for it.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_71_BergHome</column_1><column_2>Days later, you return to your senses, neatly tucked into your bed at your home in Berg. It seems that someone brought you home, and Rissa or one of her attendants nursed you back to health from the brink of death.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_72_BurningMenDefeat</column_1><column_2>The smell of your own sizzling flesh wakes you, in agonizing pain. Burning Men walk nearby, almost oblivious to your presence. You don’t know why they’ve taken you prisoner, but given that they tried to set you on fire...You clearly don’t want to find out.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_73_HiveMenDefeat</column_1><column_2>Something bitter trickles from your mouth as you wake, cocooned by venomous insect creatures. As you free yourself, you can feel their poison coursing through your veins. You may not have much time left before the poison takes you...</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_74_ThirstTuto</column_1><column_2>Your injured body can take no more, and you pass out from the continued trauma. When your eyes open once more, you are safe at a campsite along the beach. You vow to take better care of yourself in the future.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_301_BCQ1_DefeatByLevantAgents</column_1><column_2>Your head throbs as you pull yourself up. Gabriella Sullivan gives you a little patronizing wave from nearby. It would seem she saved your life from the criminals who have attacked the Blue Chamber.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_302_BCQ1_DefeatByLevantScouts</column_1><column_2>You come to, tied to a stake not far from the outpost, left for the beasts and Burning Men to finish off. Fortunately, they ignore you as you free yourself from the stake and arm yourself for another round!</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_303_BCQ1_DefeatByLevantScoutsLeader</column_1><column_2>You brace yourself for the killing blow, but it does not come. You crack an eye open to see your foe fleeing at full speed. In your state, you will never catch up to him...It would seem that the one who led the assault on Berg has gotten away.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_304_BCQ2_DefeatByCyr</column_1><column_2>You wonder what you were thinking, as Cyr lifts you up with one hand. He makes a loud, rousing speech to his people in the giant’s tongue, then he walks right to the gates of his village and hurls you as far as he can. As you hit the ground, the doors slam shut for good.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_305_BCQ3_DefeatByRoland</column_1><column_2>As Roland’s possessed body approaches for the killing blow, you see him for a moment regain control and hold himself back. You take this as your cue to flee for your life to a safe part of the Necropolis to tend to your wounds.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_306_BCQ4_DefeatByBattleborn-01</column_1><column_2>You awaken in one of the beds in Berg's inn, suffering from a broken rib. The news you hear as you recover is grim indeed, Sagard Battleborn has gone rogue with a large battalion of the army. They will likely be a thorn in everyone’s side for a very long time to come.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_306_BCQ4_DefeatByBattleborn-02</column_1><column_2>Berg falls into a brief period of chaos without it’s Chamberlord, but by the time you can walk again, Gabriella Sullivan has been chosen to be Chamberlady. She seems none too pleased, but life in Berg will go on.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_307_BCQ4_DefeatByMonsoonHorrors</column_1><column_2>Cheers make you open your eyes through the haze of pain. It would seem the battle is over, and you’ve been dragged to the side with the other injured. While you’re disappointed you missed the end of the fight, as least you’re still alive to tell the tale.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_308_HMQ1_DefeatByGhosts</column_1><column_2>Screams rip from your throat as the corrupted ghosts plunder your life force greedily. Suddenly, a blast of light fills the room, and you see Oliele’s blade cut through your attackers. As you struggle to get up, you see that your friend’s ruined body has been forever changed...</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_309_HMQ3_DefeatByRebelPriests</column_1><column_2>You feel Soeran patching up your injuries as you slowly regain consciousness. A quick glance around confirms that it was a massacre. Not a single one of the rebel priests is still alive. Oliele has completely vanished. Is seems she has forever abandoned the Holy Mission...</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_310_HMQ4_DefeatByBattlebornThugs</column_1><column_2>You haul yourself to your feet, beaten and bloody. Those thugs from the Blue Chamber Collective beat you to within an inch of your life, then slaughtered the prisoners...Elatt will no doubt be upset.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_311_HMQ5_DefeatByImmaculate</column_1><column_2>As the Immaculates pounce on you without mercy, the ground beneath you crumbles, and you fall into darkness. By the time you pull yourself out, your foes seem to have regained their senses and fled the cave. They will no doubt be a danger to Monsoon in the future.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_312_LQ1_DefeatByLevantAgents</column_1><column_2>You cough up soot and ash as you wake up. The chamber is caked in dust, and a large hole yawns wide in the wall above you. The attackers seem to have detonated an explosive and left you to take the blame...</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_313_LQ2_DefeatByBCScoots</column_1><column_2>You cough up sand as you stir from unconsciousness. 殴られて出血までしているが、まだ生きている。
It would seem that those Blue Chamber Scouts still uphold the tradition of not killing foes unless truly needed, or they mistook your for dead.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_314_LQ4_DefeatBySoldiers</column_1><column_2>You open your eyes in the abandoned docks, inches from death. You have no idea how long you’ve been out, but by now the coup against Levant is likely in full swing. You should hurry if you intend to stop them!</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_315_LQ4_DefeatByCyrene</column_1><column_2>You open your eyes, and can tell by the stench that you’ve been thrown onto a pile of corpses. It seems Cyrene mistook you for dead.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_316_LQ5_DefeatDuringPrinceFight</column_1><column_2>The bustle of the Levantine Palace rouses you. From the chatter around you, you can guess that the raid against the Prince was successful, despite your injury. An aide informs you that the Queen wishes to reward your service. You should speak with her once you’ve recovered.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_318_HMQ1_DefeatByCorruption</column_1><column_2>Corrupted Ghosts surge from the Altar, their emergence blasting you away. Oliele drops to the floor, her veins turning a sick glowing green from the Corruption she absorbed. These twisted Ghosts crave your very life! You must defend yourself!</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_3120_HMQ4_TrueDeath_01</column_1><column_2>We've all dreamed of being heroes, haven't we? Chosen by destiny, given sacred protection, unrivaled ability...</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_3120_HMQ4_TrueDeath_02</column_1><column_2>Divine heroes walk among us, and for a brief moment, you were one of them. You gave your mortal life so that another could live.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_3120_HMQ4_TrueDeath_03</column_1><column_2>Even now, as your vision dims forever, the impact of your deed remains a key part of the history of Aurai.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>DS_3120_HMQ4_TrueDeath_04</column_1><column_2>Even now, as you feel yourself be pulled towards what lies beyond, to join your ancestors...You can't help but feel pride at what you accomplished.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>Camping_NoEvent</column_1><column_2>Fortunately, your rest goes without incident and you feel better prepared for the day ahead.</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>Camping_Ambush</column_1><column_2>Your rest is interrupted by the faintest of unnatural sounds! You scramble to protect yourself from the ambush!</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>Prologue_1</column_1><column_2>私はいままでCierzoで安全に生活をし、外の世界の残虐さからは免れてきた。だがAuraiでの暮らしは楽ではなかった。全ては安全の為、我々の部族は苛烈な法を強いている。我々は個人ではなく、血統で審判を下されるのだ。</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>Prologue_2</column_1><column_2>血統の失敗が私に重くのしかかった。祖母が過去に部族を没落させ、一族の血の価値も酷く落としたのだ。それ以来、我々はその責任として借金を払わされ続けている。</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>Prologue_3</column_1><column_2>私は旧友のYzanと共に、借金を帳消しにするだけの金銭を求め、海を渡って遠征に参加した。これが間違いだった。帰航の際に船が座礁したのだ。私がまだ息をしているのが僅かながらの幸運だろう。</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
    <ooo_row><column_1>Prologue_4</column_1><column_2>今や、私には未開の地、壁の向こう側に向かう以外に選択肢はない。自分自身の未来を切り開くか、いっそ死ぬかだ。</column_2><column_3/><column_4/><column_5/><column_6/></ooo_row>
  </ooo_sheet>
</ooo_calc_export>